Design For Living. Yvonne speaking.
家居设计公司，我是Yvonne.
Bill Collins! How are you?
Bill Collins! 你好吗?
Fine. Great.
We're very busy working.
我们的工作非常忙，
But we always have time for you.
不过对你我们总是有时间的.
You're buying a house?
你要买房子了?
Fabulous. Of course we're interested.
太棒了. 我们当然感兴趣.
Why don't you stop by next Wednesday.
你何不下星期三过来坐一会儿?
Two o'clock? Terrific. See you then.
两点钟? 好极了. 到时候见.
-What? -We can't do it.
-What? -这活儿我们不能接.
We can't not do it.
我们不能不接这个活儿.
Yvonne. Work is good. Killing ourselves is bad.
Yvonne. 有活儿干当然好. 苦了我们自己可就不好了.
Turning away clients is bad.
把上门的客户回绝掉才不好.
We like Bill. This is good news.
我们都喜欢Bill，这可是好消息.
Yes. We like Bill. I also like eating and sleeping.
Yes. 我们是喜欢Bill. 可是我也喜欢吃, 喜欢睡.
And it's very pleasant every once in a while to take a vacation.
如果还能时不时地度度假的话，那就太美了.
What are you? afraid of success?
你怎么啦? 害怕成功吗?
Oh please.
It's no use complaining, is it?
抱怨是没有用的，不是吗?
Nope. You'll thank me later.
Nope.你以后会感谢我的.
I know. That's what kills me.
我知道. 那才是让我痛苦的事.